export function manageResponse(responseType, firm){
    return function(response) {
        if(response.ok){
            return response[responseType]();
        }
        else{
            return Promise.reject(response);
        }
    };
}

export function getParameter(name, url){
    name = name.replace(/[\[\]]/g, '\\$&');
    let regex = new RegExp('[?&]' + name + '(=([^&#]*)|&|#|$)'),
    results = regex.exec(url);
    if (!results){
        return null;
    }
    if (!results[2]){
        return '';
    }
    return decodeURIComponent(results[2].replace(/\+/g, ' '));
}

export let pokeTest = [
    {
        question: 'ğŸŒ· ğŸŒ¸ ğŸŒ± \n ğŸ¸ ğŸŠ ğŸ‰',
        answer: 'Venusaur',
    },
    {
        question: 'ğŸ”¥ ğŸŒ‹ ğŸ‡\nğŸ¸ ğŸŠ ğŸ‰',
        answer: 'Charizard'
    },
    {
        question: 'ğŸŒŠ ğŸ’§ ğŸ’¦\n ğŸ¢ ğŸ¢ ğŸ¢',
        answer: 'Blastoise'
    },
    {
        question: 'ğŸ”ª ğŸ ğŸ”ª',
        answer: 'Beedrill'
    },
    {
        question: 'ğŸ­ ğŸ‘¹ ğŸ’¨ ğŸ­',
        answer: 'Koffing'
    },
    {
        question: 'âš¡ï¸ ğŸ­ âš¡ï¸',
        answer: 'Pikachu'
    },
    {
        question: 'ğŸ§ ğŸ¥ ğŸ¹',
        answer: 'Jigglypuff'
    },
    {
        question: 'ğŸ„ ğŸœ ğŸ„',
        answer: 'Parras'
    },
    {
        question: 'ğŸµ ğŸµ ğŸµ ğŸµ ğŸ’© ğŸµ',
        answer: 'Ditto'
    },
    {
        question: 'ğŸ”¥ ğŸˆ ğŸ”¥',
        answer: 'Growlithe'
    },
    {
        question: 'ğŸ”¥ ğŸ… ğŸ”¥',
        answer: 'Arcanine'
    },
    {
        question: 'ğŸ’ªğŸ¿ ğŸŒš',
        answer: 'Geodude'
    },
    {
        question: 'ğŸ· ğŸš',
        answer: 'Slowbro'
    },
    {
        question: '  ğŸ’€\nğŸ”¨ ğŸ­',
        answer: 'Cubone'
    },
    {
        question: 'ğŸ·\nğŸ³',
        answer: 'Chansey'
    },
    {
        question: 'ğŸ‘€\nâ­•ï¸\nğŸ‘—',
        answer: 'Jynx'
    }
];
